Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive, 1989-2004 MSS.191
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: The Beat Experience / Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Ndegocello, Me'Shell, 1995; cuid7669 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Nicosia, Gerald, 1995; cuid7670 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Notes, "John's", 1995; cuid7671 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Notes, Lisa [Hacken]'s (Research coordinator), 1995; cuid7672 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Offbeat Archive, [n.d.]; cuid7673 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Paid Invoices (Restricted), 1995; cuid7674 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Pending / Money received, 1995; cuid7675 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Publishing, 1995 - 1996; cuid7676 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Red Hot and Beat, 1995; cuid7677 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Royalty statement, 1996 - 1997; cuid7678 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Shapero, Alyson (Marketing consultant) (Restricted), 1996; cuid7679 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Skylab, 1996; cuid7680 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Stills, 1995; cuid7681 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Includes listing of images to appear on CD-ROM and photocopies of two Dennis Hopper images. Also includes correspondence and agreements to obtain permission rights for said images.
    - Stills, 1995-1996; cuid7682 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Includes photocopies of 11 images featuring Kerouac, Ginsberg, Burroughs and more. Also includes correspondence and agreements to obtain permission rights for images appearing on CD-ROM.
    - Synchronization licenses, 1995 - 1996; cuid7683 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Text, 1995-1996; cuid7684 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Includes text and images to appear on CD-ROM. Also includes correspondence and agreements to obtain permission rights for said text and images.
    - Text, 1995-1996; cuid7685 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - TVT Records, 1996; cuid7686 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Video tracking log, 1995 - 1996; cuid7687 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - The Voyager Company, 1996 - 1997; cuid7688 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Wax Trax Records / TVT Records (label), 1995 - 1996; cuid7689 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Fliers for "Offbeat: A Red Hot Happening" and "The Beat Experience", cuid7690 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Mousepads labeled "BEATPAD" featuring Sue Coe drawing, 1995; cuid7691 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Postcard invitations to exhibition of work by Gary Panter and David Sandlin "to celebrate the release of THE BEAT EXPERIENCE CD-ROM/VIDEO and OFFBEAT ENHANCED AUDIO CD", c.a. 1996; cuid7692 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Press clippings, 1995-1996; cuid7693 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Press clippings, compilation of 1996, cuid7694 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Press release, 1995; cuid7695 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Promotional: The Beat Experience, 1995; cuid7696 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Stickers, [n.d.]; cuid7697 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Negatives: Sue Coe artwork, 1995; cuid7698 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Slides (black and white): Mostly portraits of artistes, cuid7699 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Slides (color): Offbeat and The Beat Experience covers, cuid7700 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - The Beat Experience, 1996; cuid7701 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Compact disc read-only memory
    - The Beat Experience, 1995; cuid7702 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Offbeat: A Red Hot Sound Trip, 1996; cuid7703 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Enhanced audio compact disc
- Series IX: America Is Dying Slowly
  America Is Dying Slowly was released in 1996 by Eastwest Records America. It features hip hop producers and rappers who had not previously worked together. (Reference: http://redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - 8Ball & MJG, 1996; cuid7704 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - America@ (RHO#7), 1994-1996; cuid7705 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      SyQuest 45 MB Removable Hard Disk
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7706 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Biz Markie, 1996; cuid7707 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Brian, 1996; cuid7708 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Buckwild, 1995-1996; cuid7709 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Cashflow/budget, 1992; cuid7710 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Clearances, 1995-1996; cuid7711 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Clearances, 1995-1996; cuid7712 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Clearances, 1995-1996; cuid7713 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Common Sense, 1995-1996; cuid7714 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Contact info, [n.d.]; cuid7715 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Contract copies, 1995-1996; cuid7716 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Coolio (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7717 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - De La Soul (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7718 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Development budget, 1992; cuid7719 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Diamond D (Restricted), 1995; cuid7720 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Domino, 1996; cuid7721 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Elektra, 1994-1996; cuid7722 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Expenses, 1995-1996; cuid7723 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Expenses, 1995-1996; cuid7724 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Expenses: Recording sessions, 1996; cuid7725 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Famous Artists Agency, Inc.: Checks from De La Soul/Fishbone/Goodie Mob tour, 1997; cuid7726 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Fat Joe, 1996; cuid7727 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Financial statements, 1996-1998; cuid7728 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - The Jungle Brothers, 1995; cuid7729 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Kool G Rap, 1995-1996; cuid7730 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Label contracts, 1995-1996; cuid7731 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - The Lost Boyz, 1995-1996; cuid7732 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Mac Mall (Restricted), 1996; cuid7733 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Masta Ace (Restricted), 1995; cuid7734 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - MC Lyte (Restricted), 1995; cuid7735 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Mobb Deep (Restricted), 1995; cuid7736 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Money Boss Players (Restricted), 1995; cuid7737 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - O.C., 1996; cuid7738 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Organized Konfusion (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7739 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Paid bills, 1998-1999; cuid7740 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Panasonic TV commercial, 1993; cuid7741 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Prince Paul, 1995-1996; cuid7742 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Producer contracts, 1995-1996; cuid7743 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Publishing, 1995-1996; cuid7744 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Red Hot # 18, 1993-1996; cuid7745 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Return to Helene Silverman / Final "America is Dying Slowly" Artwork, 1994-1996; cuid7746 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Royalties: "I Breaks 'Em Off" / "The Hustle", 1996-1997; cuid7747 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - RZA, 1995-1996; cuid7748 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Samples, 1995-1996; cuid7749 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Session reports (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7750 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Skadanks, 1995-1996; cuid7751 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Special Ed, 1995; cuid7752 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Spice 1, 1996; cuid7753 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Usless, 1995-1996; cuid7754 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Video expenses, 1995-1996; cuid7755 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7756 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Wu-Tang Clan, 1995-1996; cuid7757 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Condoms - America is Dying Slowly, 1996; cuid7758 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Flier ad for "America is Dying Slowly" record release party, 1996; cuid7759 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Press clippings, 1996; cuid7760 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Press clippings, 1996; cuid7761 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Promos & Show, [n.d.]; cuid7762 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - America Is Dying Slowly; EastWest Records America, 1996; cuid7763 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - America Is Dying Slowly; EastWest Records America, 1996; cuid7764 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Series X: Red Hot + Rio
  Red Hot + Rio was released by VERVE ANTILLES in 1996 and is a tribute to the Bossa Nova sound, with a focus on compositions by Antonio Carlos Jobim. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Advance from PolyGram Records, Inc., 1995; cuid7765 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Airto / Flora Purim, 1994-1996; cuid7766 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Artist agreements, 1994-1997; cuid7767 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7768 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - "The Bachelor" soundtrack, 1999-2000; cuid7769 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Banana Republic - paid bills, 1998-1999; cuid7770 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Banana Republic sync, 1999; cuid7771 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Banana Republic's "Chinos" television campaign, 1999; cuid7772 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Bjork + Eumir Deodato, 1995-1996; cuid7773 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Bravo Company, 1996-1997; cuid7774 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Brazil II, 1995-1996; cuid7775 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Carlinhos, 1995-1996; cuid7776 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Budget and reimbursements from PolyGram Records (label) - Nova Bossa: Red Hot On Verve, 1996; cuid7777 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Byrne, David, 1995-1997; cuid7778 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Cazuza: Som Livre, 1995-1996; cuid7779 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Chico Science / Goldie Co Production, 1996; cuid7780 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Record labels, 1996 - 1999; cuid7781 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Crystal Waters (Restricted), 1996; cuid7782 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - DJ Soul Slinger, 1996; cuid7783 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Everything but the Girl, 1995-1996; cuid7784 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Everything but the Girl, 1995-1996; cuid7785 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Évora, Cesária, 1996; cuid7786 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Foreign sales breakdown, 1997; cuid7787 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Gil, Gilberto, 1993-1996; cuid7788 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Gilberto, Bebel, 1996; cuid7789 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Hotoda, Goh, 1996; cuid7790 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Incognito, 1996-1997; cuid7791 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Invoices (Restricted), 1996; cuid7792 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Jobim, Antonio Carlos, 1994; cuid7793 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Label agreements, 1996-1997; cuid7794 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Licensing, 1996-1998; cuid7795 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Mad Professor, 1996; cuid7796 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Mathewman, S., 1996; cuid7797 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Maxwell (Restricted), 1996; cuid7798 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Michael, George, 1995-1996; cuid7799 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Money Mark, 1996; cuid7800 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Monte, Marisa, 1995-1996; cuid7801 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - MTV Brasil, 1996-1999; cuid7802 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Nascimento, Milton, 1995-1997; cuid7803 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - P.M. Dawn + Flora Purim, 1995-1996; cuid7804 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Profit and loss statement, 1997; cuid7805 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Promotional CD collaboration with Mossimo and Details magazine, 1997; cuid7806 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Publishing, 1995-1997; cuid7807 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Red Hot + Rio, 1994-1996; cuid7808 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Red Hot 16, 1993-1996; cuid7809 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Royalty statements - Nova Bossa: Red Hot On Verve, 1998 - 2003; cuid7810 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Sakamoto, Ryuichi, 1996; cuid7811 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Samples, 1996; cuid7812 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Skylab, 1996; cuid7813 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Stereolab, 1995-1996; cuid7814 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Stereolab, 1996; cuid7815 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Sting / Jobim, Antonio Carlos, 1995-1997; cuid7816 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Track by track, 1995-2000; cuid7817 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Veloso, Caetano, 1993; cuid7818 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Verve Records (Restricted), 1993-2000; cuid7819 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Video tracking log, bulk 1996; cuid7820 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Wheeler, Caron, 1996; cuid7821 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Wieden & Kennedy - Zima, 1998-1999; cuid7822 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Williams, Vanessa (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7823 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Williams, Vanessa (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7824 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Williams, Vanessa / Prince Charles Remix, 1996; cuid7825 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Cardboard ad - Red Hot + Rio, 1996; cuid7826 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Fliers - Red Hot + Rio, 1996; cuid7827 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Invitation envelope to Red Hot + Rio event, [n.d.]; cuid7828 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Invitation to Red Hot + Rio event, 1996; cuid7829 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Mossimo Music, in collaboration with Details magazine (Promotional), 1997; cuid7830 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Music You Haven't Heard Yet: Vol 2; Antilles Records (Promotional), 1996; cuid7831 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Postcard ads - Red Hot + Rio, 1996; cuid7832 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Press clippings (English), 1996 - 1997; cuid7833 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Press clippings (Other languages), 1996 - 1997; cuid7834 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Red Hot + Rio; Antilles /Verve Records (Promotional), 1996; cuid7835 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Sticker ads - Red Hot + Rio, 1996; cuid7836 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Sticker buttons - Red Hot + Rio, [n.d.]; cuid7837 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Nova Bossa: Red Hot On Verve; PolyGram Records, 1996; cuid7838 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Red Hot + Rio; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996; cuid7839 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Red Hot + Rio; Antilles /Verve Records, 1996; cuid7840 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Red Hot + Rio, Japanese edition; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996; cuid7841 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Audio sound disc
    - Single (2 tracks): "The Boy from Ipanema," Crystal Waters; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996; cuid7842 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Single (4 tracks): "The Boy from Ipanema," Crystal Waters; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996; cuid7843 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Series XI: Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin
  Silencio = Muerte: Red Hot + Latin was originally released in 1997 on Jellybean Benitez' H.O.L.A Recordings. In celebration of the album's ten-year anniversary, it was re-released in 2006 as Red Hot + Latin Redux by Nacional Records, featuring new bonus tracks and remastered tracks from the original release. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Advances from H.O.L.A Records (label), 1996; cuid7844 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Agreements, 1996-1997; cuid7845 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Artist agreements, 1996-1997; cuid7846 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Aterciopelados, 1998; cuid7847 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7848 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Budget + Expenses (Restricted), 1996-1997; cuid7849 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Contact information, 1996-1997; cuid7850 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Cookman International, 1996; cuid7851 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Cost analysis, 1996 - 1999; cuid7852 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Label agreements, 1996-1997; cuid7853 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Latin, 1996-1997; cuid7854 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Publishing, 1996-1997; cuid7855 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Samples, 1996; cuid7856 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Track by track, 1996-1997; cuid7857 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7858 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Flier ads - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin, 1997; cuid7859 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Postcard ads (big) - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin, 1997; cuid7860 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Postcard ads (small) - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin, 1997; cuid7861 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Press clippings (English), 1997; cuid7862 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Press clippings (Other languages), 1997; cuid7863 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional), 1996; cuid7864 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by Café Tacuba and David Byrne, 1996; cuid7865 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by Cibo Matto, 1996; cuid7866 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by Geggy Tah, 1996; cuid7867 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by King Changó, 1996; cuid7868 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Simon Says, Volume Ten, Summer 1997; cuid7869 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Temporary tattoos - Silencio=Muerte, [n.d.]; cuid7870 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Slides: Album cover, [n.d.]; cuid7871 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records, 1996; cuid7872 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin CD liner notes, 1996; cuid7873 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Lain Redux; Nacional Records, 2006; cuid7874 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Series XII: Every Nation (from "Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute"), 1997
  Every Nation is a song composed by R. Kelly and included in the tribute album "Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute." (Sony, 1997) Various artists contributed to the track, and they were collectively credited as "Red Hot R+B All Stars." (Reference: Amazon.com)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Accounting, 1997; cuid7875 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Clearances (Restricted), 1997-1998; cuid7876 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Contracts (Restricted), 1997; cuid7877 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Di, Di, Di, 1997; cuid7878 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Evans, Faith, 1997; cuid7879 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Expenses etc. (Restricted), 1996-2000; cuid7880 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Video tracking log, 1997 - 1998; cuid7881 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 1997; cuid7882 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute; Sony, 1997; cuid7883 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Every Nation; Sony, 1997; cuid7884 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Selections from Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute; Sony, 1997; cuid7885 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Series XIII: Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon
  Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon was released in 1998 by Bar/None in North America, Movieplay Portuguesa in Europe, and Trama in Brasil. The album features 40 artists from 11 countries singing in 7 languages, and was created in conjunction with the 1998 World Expo in Lisbon Portugal. A donation of $100,000 was made in Red Hot's name by Imperio Seguradora. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - 98 Expo (paid bills) (Restricted), 1997-1998; cuid7886 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - 98 Expo (paid bills) (Restricted), 1998-1999; cuid7887 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Advance, 1999; cuid7888 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Agreements, 1997-1999; cuid7889 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7890 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Bar/None Records, 1998-1999; cuid7891 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Bar/None Records, 1999; cuid7892 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Bar/None Records invoices, 1999; cuid7893 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Budget (Restricted), 1997-1999; cuid7894 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Budget (Restricted), 1997-1999; cuid7895 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - CD-R containing folders named "LISBOA R.Hot," "Red Hot + lisbon" and more, cuid7896 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      CD-R: 650 MB.
    - Contacts (Restricted), 1998; cuid7897 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1998; cuid7898 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Grants, 2000; cuid7899 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Marketing - to bill, 1999; cuid7900 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Miranda, Carmen, 1998; cuid7901 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - MuchMusic Network, 2000; cuid7902 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - MuchMusic Network, Lisbon TV, 1999-2000; cuid7903 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Petty cash report for TV special production, 1998; cuid7904 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - PR / Song by song, [n.d.]; cuid7905 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Production budget / expenses, 1998; cuid7906 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - To Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company, 1998; cuid7907 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Track by track (Restricted), 1997-1998; cuid7908 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Trama Promocoes Artisticas Ltda, 1999; cuid7909 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - TV budget, 1998; cuid7910 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - TV clip releases, 1998; cuid7911 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - TV releases (Restricted), 1998; cuid7912 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - TWISTED America Records, 1997; cuid7913 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - US $$$, 1999; cuid7914 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7915 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings (English), 1999; cuid7916 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings (Other languages), 1998; cuid7917 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Stickers - Onda Sonora, cuid7918 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Stickers - Onda Sonora, cuid7919 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon; Bar/None Records, 1998; cuid7920 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Series XIV: Red Hot + Rhapsody
  Red Hot + Rhapsody, a George Gershwin tribute album, was released by Verve/Antilles in 1998. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Agreements (Restricted), 1997-1999; cuid7921 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Artist agreements (Restricted), 1997-1999; cuid7922 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - [Artist information], [n.d.]; cuid7923 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7924 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Badalementi, Angelo, 1998; cuid7925 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Bills (Restricted), 1994-1999; cuid7926 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Budget / Expenses, 1998-1999; cuid7927 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - By George (& Ira): Red Hot on Gershwin, 1998; cuid7928 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Contacts, 1998; cuid7929 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Dando, Evan (Restricted), 1998; cuid7930 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Details - Levis, 1998; cuid7931 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Crew passes for "Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody", [n.d.]; cuid7932 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - General ledger, 1998; cuid7933 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Invoices, 1998-1999; cuid7934 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Liner notes for George Gershwin: Works for Orchestra & for Piano & Orchestra, [n.d.]; cuid7935 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Live event agreements (Restricted), 1998; cuid7936 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Live show, 1998; cuid7937 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Luscious Jackson (Restricted), 1998; cuid7938 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Marketing, 1998; cuid7939 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Merchant, Natalie, 1998; cuid7940 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Morcheeba (video) - paid bills, 1998-1999; cuid7941 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Much Music Network broadcast payment, 2000; cuid7942 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - O'Connor, Sinead, 1997; cuid7943 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - On Gershwin contract, 1996-1999; cuid7944 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Paid bills (Restricted), 1998-1999; cuid7945 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Paid bills (Restricted), 1998-2000; cuid7946 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Quaye, Finley / Ernest Ranglin, 1997-1998; cuid7947 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Rhapsody (contents: Samples, By George, Details Releases & Verve Memos) (Restricted), 1998-1999; cuid7948 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Session book / Jamaica, 1997-1998; cuid7949 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Summertime, 1998-2003; cuid7950 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - To do ..., 1998-1999; cuid7951 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - TV budget, 1998; cuid7952 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - TV expenses, 1998; cuid7953 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - TV invoices (Restricted), 1998-1999; cuid7954 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - TV waivers (Restricted), 1998; cuid7955 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Verve - Rhapsody marketing, 1998; cuid7956 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Video shoot / Morcheeba (Restricted), 1998; cuid7957 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Video tracking log, 1998; cuid7958 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Womack, Bobby w/ Automator, 1998; cuid7959 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Details magazine, November 1998; cuid7960 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Details Magazine Salutes Red Hot & Rhapsody: Banner, [n.d.]; cuid7961 (Oversize 10 West)